So, hello everyone in this video, we are going to start with the chat store file.
So in this one, as you can see that in the front end, wait a second, let me close this
back end.
So it looks good.
So in this store, as you can see, that authstore.js file is present.
So for the chat, cut there, we are out to make one chatstore.js.
After this, we are going to use the dewstand right for this one also.
So import create from dewstand.
After this, we are going to import the toast from the React Autost.
So import those from React Autost.
After this, we are going to just use the XUS instance.
This is from the live XUS.
So after this, we are going to export a function.
So export Chats store equals to create, and we are going to use the set.
So let's use one callback.
And now inside of this, we will make one user's array, which is empty.
And after this, we are going to use this get users.
It would be a function, it will call back function.
So after this, let's wrap this thing up in the try and catch block.
So try and catch, so try and catch, for if some error arises, so we are going to catch it
in this block.
So now after this, in a try, we are going to hit the end point, const r is equal to
await XUS instance dot get, and after this slash message is user.
So I believe, and one more thing if I remember that in this XUS instance, this is
wrong, but this route actually in the messages in the backend, I have done it for the post
I guess if I remember correctly.
So in the backend, let's go to this message controller, not message controller, actually
message routes.
Yeah, that's one problem.
So put this here as get, okay.
Now after this, let's go back again with that.
So try, we are getting the response.
Set this one.
So set users, response dot data, okay.
So after this, we are going to just say toast dot success, and inside of this, we are just
going to say that users, fetched successfully, success fully, okay.
And in the cache block, same thing.
So if some errorizes in that case, we are going to use the error message from the toast.
That is to start error failed to fetch users, okay.
There's some problem.
I guess there should not be one problem, but why it's showing like this, okay.
That's fine.
Control has saved and for this one, console dot log, we can use the error itself, so error.
So all the errors are gone.
So we have made this chat store dot JS file, okay.
And now after this, what we are actually going to do?
So let me think, yeah.
So I have this sideboard dot TXT file, okay.
So this text file, we are going to use like this JSX, we are going to use a control C, and
we can paste this inside of the, let's create one file in the component, okay.
So components side bar dot, so side bar, side bar dot JSX, and let's control paste it
here, okay.
So this side bar component had some problems, okay.
So I'm going to fix it all.
So for the starter files, you can actually use this, no issues, so, okay.
So for this one, go inside of the homepage and since there is nothing, so let's import
this one, so side bar control as it's imported saved.
So we imported this, so I will check up on this side bar, okay.
I will fix it and we will continue to work on this side bar in the next video, thanks.